♪No matter how far the road is, don’t be afraid♪
♪길이 아무리 멀더라도 두려워하지 마세요♪
♪Love is gentle and caring♪
♪사랑은 부드럽고 배려심이 깊습니다♪
♪Those wounds will definitely scab over♪
♪그 상처는 반드시 딱지가 될 거야♪
♪Everything gathers into the flower of time♪
♪모든 것은 시간의 꽃으로 모인다♪
♪ Someone will pick it up for you eventually ♪
♪결국 누군가가 당신을 대신해 가져갈 거예요♪
♪Keep going, you won’t be alone♪
♪계속 가세요. 당신은 혼자가 아닐 거예요♪
♪Conversation with time♪
♪시간과 함께 이야기 나누기♪
♪The light falls gently, just take it as her answer♪
♪빛이 살며시 내리는 걸 그녀의 대답이라고 생각해♪
♪May you have him in the sea of ​​people♪
♪그를 사람들의 바다 속에 두시기를 바랍니다 ♪
♪Live a simple and peaceful life♪
♪ 간단하고 평화로운 삶을 살아보세요♪
♪Understand that life is full of regrets♪
♪인생은 후회로 가득 차 있다는 것을 이해하세요♪
♪But, you still love♪
♪하지만 당신은 여전히 ​​사랑해요♪
♪This winter and summer♪
♪이번 겨울과 여름♪
[Love is the panacea] [Episode 4]
[사랑은 만병통치약] [4회]
[2022 Sichuan Province Characteristic Support Artworks]
[ 2022년 쓰촨성 지원 예술 작품 소개 ]
[Diadaptasi dari novel "Zhi Yu Zhe" karya Ning Meng Xi Yan]
[Diadaptasi dari 소설 "Zhi Yu Zhe" karya Ning Meng Xi Yan]
[Lakaya] [Operating Room]
[라카야] [수술실]
Damn it!
젠장!
Now I'm still in the hospital.
지금은 아직 병원에 있어요.
Why did the police want my blood test results?
경찰은 왜 내 혈액검사 결과를 가지고 있나요?
Which Chinese woman intervened?
어느 중국 여성이 개입했나요?
Don't let me meet him.
내가 그 사람을 만나지 못하게 해주세요.
This is your medicine for five days.
이것이 5일분의 약입니다.
Okay, I already knew that.
알았어, 난 이미 알고 있어.
Aura.
후광.
Are you the Chinese woman who helped me before?
당신은 이전에 나를 도와주었던 그 중국 여자입니까 ?
not me.
나는 아니다.
However, he is my friend.
그러나 그는 내 친구입니다.
Where can I find it?
어디서 찾을 수 있나요?
what are you looking for?
무엇을 찾고 계신가요?
Of course I have to thank him.
물론 그에게 감사를 표하기 위해서다.
He saved my life.
그는 내 생명을 구했습니다.
Namanya Su Wei'an.
나만야 수웨이안.
He also works at this hospital.
그 사람도 이 병원에서 일해요.
Doctor Gu, take a look.
구 박사님, 잠시만 살펴보세요.
have a good rest.
편안히 휴식을 취하다.
You told him.
당신이 그에게 말했어요.
Post-operative recovery was excellent.
수술 후 회복은 매우 뛰어났습니다.
You can go home anytime.
언제든지 집에 갈 수 있습니다.
OK
좋은.
Post-operative recovery was excellent.
수술 후 회복은 매우 뛰어났습니다.
Here is the fee list.
비용 목록입니다.
After payment, you can go through the discharge procedures.
결제가 완료되면 병원 퇴원 절차를 처리할 수 있습니다 .
Here is your list of expenses.
이것은 귀하의 비용 목록입니다.
[Total cost after tax $10,021.15]
[세금 후 총 비용 $10,021.15]
So sad.
맙소사.
Why is it so expensive?
왜 그렇게 비싸요?
Where can I get so much money to give you?
너희들에게 그 많은 돈을 어디서 구하느냐 ?
Why save me?
왜 나를 구해?
This money should not be paid by me.
이 돈은 내가 지불하면 안 됩니다.
The Chinese woman who saved me should pay the price!
나를 구해준 중국여자가 돈을 냈어야지!
- where is he? - He's crazy.
- 그 사람은 어디 있지? - 그는 미쳤다.
Where?
어디?
Why save me?
왜 나를 구해?
Are you OK?
괜찮아요?
I am fine.
나는 괜찮아.
But will Wei An be okay?
하지만 웨이안은 괜찮겠죠?
I just said that Wei An saved him.
방금 웨이안이 그를 구했다고 말했어요 .
Why are you telling him this?
왜 그 사람에게 이런 말을 하는 거죠?
so...
그래서...
he ask me.
그는 나에게 물었다.
You tell him,
당신은 그에게 말했습니다.
I signed the medical bills.
나는 의료비에 서명하는 사람입니다.
I was the one who submitted the blood test results to the police.
혈액검사 결과를 경찰에 제출한 사람은 바로 저였습니다.
It has nothing to do with anyone else.
다른 누구와도 관련이 없습니다.
Translate what I said.
내 말대로 번역해 보세요.
what did he say?
그는 무엇을 말 했는가?
Dr. Gu
구박사
Who submits your blood test results to the police.
혈액검사 결과를 경찰에 제출하는 사람.
you?
너?
oops!
아요!
Come on, hit me.
어서, 때려요.
quickly.
빠른.
Do not touch me!
저를 만지지 마세요!
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Let me go!
날 보내줘!
Let me find that woman!
그 여자를 찾게 해주세요!
Are you that Chinese woman?
당신이 그 중국 여자인가요?
Why save me?
왜 나를 구해?
OMG.
이럴 수가.
Doctor Gu, were you okay just now?
구 박사님, 지금은 괜찮으셨나요?
I am fine.
나는 괜찮아.
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
people you helped
도와주신 분
Is a madman.
미치광이입니다.
He can't afford medical bills
그는 의료비를 지불할 수 없고,
Instead, I blame you for being too involved.
대신에 너무 관여한 것에 대해 당신을 비난합니다.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I did not do it on purpose
일부러 그런 건 아니었는데
Let him know you saved him.
당신이 그를 구했다는 것을 그에게 알려주십시오 .
Is this person still experiencing side effects from the surgery?
이 사람은 아직도 수술로 인한 부작용을 겪고 있나요 ?
Has the blood clot in your brain not been cleared yet?
뇌의 혈전이 아직 제거되지 않았습니까?
of.
의.
The surgery was very successful.
수술은 매우 성공적이었습니다.
The blood clot has been cleared .
혈전이 잘 청소되었습니다.
He can go home at any time.
그는 언제든지 집에 갈 수 있었습니다.
You know he drove drunk and caused an accident
그 사람이 음주운전을 해서 사고를 냈다는 걸 아시죠 ?
Yet such a successful operation was performed.
하지만 여전히 성공적인 작업을 수행했습니다.
As a doctor,
의사로서,
Can't decide who deserves to die.
누가 죽어야 마땅한지 결정할 수 없습니다.
You can only decide who survives.
누가 살 수 있는지 결정할 수 있습니다.
also,
뿐만 아니라,
do not you
당신은 아닌가요?
Who saved the patient?
환자를 구한 사람은 누구입니까?
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
Didn't you just ask me to tell that person?
방금 그 사람 한테 말하라고 하지 않았나요 ?
If you are the person submitting your blood test results to the police?
혈액검사 결과를 경찰에 제출한 사람이 당신이라면 ?
Why attack Wei'an now?
왜 지금 다시 웨이안을 공격하는가?
You are hurt.
당신은 다쳤어요.
It hurts, doesn't it?
아프지 않나요?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
Didn't you mean the surgeon's hands?
외과의사의 손이라고 하지 않았나요?
More valuable than gold?
금보다 더 귀한가?
how about this?
이건 어때?
I am fine.
나는 괜찮아.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Maybe it doesn't matter.
어쩌면 괜찮을 수도 있습니다.
You're bleeding too much.
당신의 피가 너무 많이 흐릅니다.
- Ayo. - Wei'an.
- 아요 - 웨이안
- You should go check with Dr. Gu immediately. - Dr. Gu.
- 구박사님께 빠르게 확인해보세요. - 구 박사님.
- Your wounds must be bandaged immediately. - I am fine.
- 상처를 즉시 붕대로 감아야 합니다. - 난 괜찮아요.
Come on, hurry up and go.
자, 빨리 가세요.
Wei An, please leave quickly.
웨이안 씨, 빨리 가세요.
It's enough.
이미 충분합니다.
The head nurse and others are very professional.
수석 간호사와 다른 사람들은 매우 전문적입니다.
Let them do it.
그들이 그렇게 하도록 놔두세요.
You are too stubborn to compromise.
당신은 정말 고집이 세서 타협을 할 수가 없어요.
[Where to see the night rainbow in Lakaya]
[라카야에서 밤무지개를 볼 수 있는 곳 ]
boss.
보스.
These are all my picks for French translations.
제가 선택한 프랑스어 번역가들은 모두 다음과 같습니다 .
All have overseas experience.
모두 해외 경험이 있습니다.
You just put it there.
그냥 거기에 두시면 됩니다.
This one is not bad.
이건 나쁘지 않아요.
Age 28 years old.
28세.
Graduate of Beijing Foreign Studies University,
북경외국어대학교 졸업 ,
Majored in French.
프랑스어를 전공합니다.
[Translator resume]
[번역가 이력서]
Graduate student in Paris.
파리 대학원생.
The woman who went to school in Paris,
파리에서 학교를 다녔던 여자,
Is it possible to live in pain in Lakaya?
라카야에서 비참하게 사는 것이 가능합니까?
this.
이것.
He is 44 years old.
그는 44세입니다.
【Resume】 Looks like a diligent person.
[개인이력서] 열심히 일하는 타입인 것 같아요.
how?
어떻게?
At this age, there are parents and children,
이 나이에는 부모와 어린 자녀가 있고 ,
Can I work away from home?
집 밖에서 일할 수 있나요?
So, just this one.
그럼 이것만요.
this.
이것.
Sudahlah, Fang Mingfan.
Sudahlah, Fang Mingfan.
Looking for French translation,
프랑스어 번역가를 찾고 있습니다.
You have to look for it slowly.
천천히 검색해야 합니다.
Too much haste will not lead to good results.
서두르면 좋은 결과가 나오지 않습니다.
Finding the right person isn't easy.
맞는 것을 찾는 것이 쉽지 않습니다.
So, we have to choose the best.
그러므로 우리는 최선을 선택해야 합니다.
Choose the best.
최고를 골라라.
Before,
이전에,
You told me to find someone new immediately
당장 새로운 사람 찾아보라고 했잖아
To replace the Su translator,
번역가 Su를 대체하려면,
There's no rush now
이제 더 이상 서두를 필요가 없습니다.
Even search slowly.
천천히 검색해도 됩니다.
The boss's heart is hard to fathom.
보스의 마음은 예측하기가 매우 어렵습니다.
Is there anything else you need to do?
아직 할 일이 더 있나요?
boss.
보스.
Look no further. check it out.
더 이상 보지 마십시오. 이것 좀 보세요.
I actually have feelings for some of them
나는 실제로이 사람들 중 일부에 대해 느낍니다.
Pretty good.
꽤 좋은.
These two are as good as Translator Su.
이 두 사람은 번역가 수만큼 훌륭합니다.
How about choosing between two alternatives?
두 가지 대안을 선택하는 것은 어떻습니까?
What if translator Su resigns one day?
만약 수 번역가가 어느 날 사임한다면 어떻게 될까요?
After all, translators’ salaries are not high.
결국 번역가의 급여는 크지 않습니다.
These two people, right?
이 두 사람 맞죠?
OK
좋은.
If you think they're good enough,
당신이 그들이 충분히 좋다고 생각한다면,
i can consider
고려해 볼 수 있어요
Replace Jiang Translator.
장 번역가를 대체했습니다.
unnecessary.
필요 없음.
I think this is good enough.
나는 그것이 충분하다고 생각합니다.
The translator Su is quite good.
Su 번역가는 꽤 좋습니다.
No need to change.
변경할 필요가 없습니다.
I'm leaving first, boss.
먼저 갈게요, 보스.
Mari, Wei'an.
마리, 웨이안.
This is physical tea
스태미나 차 입니다
That Dr. Gu asked me to soak it for you.
구 박사님이 나에게 당신을 위해 양조해 달라고 부탁한 것입니다.
After drinking it, your enthusiasm and energy will be doubled.
마시고 나면 열정과 에너지가 두 배로 커집니다.
Right or wrong?
참인가, 거짓인가?
(See. You still need my help, right?)
(봐. 아직도 내 도움이 필요하지?)
OK
멋진.
Yeah, Kan?
응, 칸?
What's this?
이게 뭔가요?
Cabinda bark.
카빈다 나무껍질.
What’s wrong with you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
what happen.
무슨 일이야.
Cabinda bark?
카빈다 나무껍질?
correct.
옳은.
this.
이것.
Stop drinking.
다시는 마시지 마세요.
Why?
왜?
This is a powerful drug used by men.
이것은 남성이 사용하는 강력한 약물입니다 .
are you sure
확실합니까
Gu Yunzheng wants me to drink?
구윤정이 나한테 마실래?
Is there such a thing?
이런 게 있나요?
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
He must have been deceived by the advertising.
그는 광고를 통해 거짓말을 한 것이 틀림없습니다.
I'll ask him.
내가 그에게 물어볼게.
I asked him (past tense.
그에게 물어 보았다.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
Wei An saw that your hand was injured and you couldn't touch the water.
웨이안은 당신의 손이 다쳐서 물에 닿을 수 없는 것을 보고,
He washes and folds clothes for you on purpose,
그는 일부러 옷을 빨고 개어준다.
Let me hand it to you.
배달해 달라고 하더군요.
Why didn't he take it himself?
왜 그 사람은 직접 가져가지 않았나요?
Wei An is this person
웨이안은 사람이다
Very shy.
매우 부끄러워하는.
Just know it in your heart.
마음속으로만 알아두세요.
Oh yeah, don't ask him.
아, 그 사람한테는 묻지 마세요.
He would blame me.
그는 나를 비난할 것이다.
You tell him that he washes well.
당신은 그에게 말했지요. 그는 잘 씻었습니다.
No need to wash it next time.
다음에는 씻을 필요가 없습니다.
Jiang.
장.
You actually gave it to Su Translator
실제로 번역가에게 Su를 주셨습니다.
Drink the bark of the cabinda tree?
카빈다 나무껍질을 마셔요?
bad.
나쁜.
The reputation of the boss lasts a lifetime
상사의 평판은 평생이다
It has been destroyed by you.
그것은 당신에 의해 파괴되었습니다.
I have no idea.
모르겠습니다.
I saw it written at the kiosk
키오스크에 써있는 걸 봤는데
Youthful and anti-fatigue.
젊고 피로하지 않습니다.
So, I bought it immediately.
그래서 바로 구매했습니다.
who knows.
누가 알아.
What do you want from all this?
이 모든 일을 해서 당신이 원하는 것은 무엇입니까 ?
I believe that the driver was the cause of the accident
운전자를 사고의 가해자로 만들었어요
Resentful of Wei An,
웨이안에게 원한을 품고,
And injured Dr. Gu's hand.
구 박사의 손을 다쳤습니다.
I want to do something for them.
나는 그들을 위해 뭔가를 하고 싶다 .
Besides, I also know Su Wei'an very well.
게다가 나는 Su Wei'an도 매우 잘 이해합니다.
Wait for it to move on its own,
스스로 움직일 때까지 기다리며,
I don't know how long I have to wait.
얼마나 기다려야 하는지 모르겠습니다.
However,
하지만,
You will only make the situation more difficult.
상황을 더욱 어렵게 만들 뿐입니다 .
Need anything more to say?
더 말할 필요가 있나요?
Annoying.
화나게 하는.
I just want to correct a mistake
단지 잘못된 점을 바로잡고 싶을 뿐입니다.
But now everything becomes more serious.
하지만 지금은 모든 것이 더욱 심각해졌습니다.
It's okay, Jiang.
괜찮아, 장.
Having friends like you ready to help,
당신처럼 언제나 도와줄 준비가 되어 있는 친구들이 있어요 .
Su Anan must be very happy.
Su Wei'an은 매우 행복할 것 같습니다.
I think you are cute.
나는 당신이 매우 귀엽다고 생각합니다.
I also want to have a father...
나도 아빠 갖고싶다...
Friends like you.
당신 같은 친구.
friend.
친구.
Aren't we already friends?
우리 둘 다 이미 친구 아닌가요?
The boss's hand is almost healed.
보스의 손이 거의 나았습니다.
How long will it take me to do laundry?
언제까지 옷을 세탁해야 하나요?
Wash until their relationship bears sweet fruit
그들의 관계가 달콤한 열매를 맺을 때까지 씻으십시오
And forever united.
그리고 영원히 하나가 되었습니다.
OK
좋은.
stop.
멈추다.
Boss, aren't you going to play on the weekend?
사장님, 주말에는 놀러 안 가시나요?
What happened to your T-shirt?
티셔츠에 무슨 문제가 있나요?
Why?
왜?
Did Su Weian wash your clothes too?
Su Wei'an도 옷을 빨았나요?
of.
의.
Yes or no.
예 혹은 아니오.
Whose clothes do you think I wash?
내가 누구 옷을 세탁한다고 하던데요?
I told you,
내가 말했잖아,
Translator Su, who loves money as much as his life,
돈을 목숨처럼 사랑하는 번역가 수 ,
Where can I do other people’s laundry for free?
다른 사람의 빨래를 무료로 도울 수 있는 곳은 어디입니까 ?
That's true.
그것은 사실이다.
Seperti Dokter Gu Yunzheng
Seperti Dokter Gu Yunzheng
They drink the bark of the cabinda tree every day,
매일 카빈다 나무껍질을 마시는 사람,
He must be in good health.
몸 상태가 아주 좋을 것 같아요.
Maybe you need someone else
어쩌면 다른 사람이 필요할지도 몰라
Help him do this kind of physical work?
이런 육체적인 일을 하도록 도와주실 건가요 ?
When did I start drinking cabinda bark?
카빈다 나무껍질은 언제부터 마시나요 ?
Jiang Muying.
장무잉.
I 'll calculate it with you later .
나중에 나는 당신과 함께 계산할 것입니다.
Su translator's time is precious;
번역가 수님의 시간은 소중하고,
I can't accept it.
나는 그것을 받아들일 수 없다.
after,
나중에,
Don't use my name to help anymore.
다시는 도움을 제공하기 위해 내 이름을 사용하지 마십시오 .
Dr. Gu is so busy
구 박사님은 너무 바빠요.
Then my question
나중에 내 문제
Doctor Gu doesn’t have to worry.
구박사님도 걱정하실 필요 없습니다.
follow me.
날 따라와.
Director Su.
수 수석.
Please have some tea.
차 좀 드세요.
What kind of tea is this?
이건 또 무슨 차야?
Answer, Chief.
대답하세요, 국장님.
This is tea
이것은 차입니다
I bought, brewed and served it myself
내가 직접 사서 끓여서 바친 것
To the chief.
대장에게.
So, absolutely no more questions.
따라서 더 이상 문제가 발생하지 않습니다.
OK, let's go.
좋아요, 가세요.
Is the chief not going to be angry with his servant again?
추장은 더 이상 하인에게 화를 내지 않죠?
If you do it again,
다시 하면,
I will punish you.
나는 당신을 처벌할 것이다.
You're too involved in your role, aren't you?
당신은 당신의 역할에 너무 몰입하고 있지 않나요?
Do you really think of yourself as the chairman?
정말로 자신이 회장이라고 생각하시나요?
I tell you, if you treat me badly again
내가 말할게, 네가 또 나한테 못되게 굴면,
I'm going to punish you, you hear me?
내가 널 벌할 거야, 들었어?
Angry at me again.
나한테 또 화내세요.
November 1st?
11월 첫째주?
Not tomorrow?
내일 아닌가요?
What important day is tomorrow?
내일은 무슨 중요한 날인가요?
Tomorrow is the market opening day
내일은 시장 개장일이에요
Champion Lakaya coffee beans.
챔피언 라카야 커피 원두.
The event starts at 7am.
행사는 아침 7시에 시작됩니다.
First come, first served.
선착순입니다.
After all, the event only happens once a year.
결국 이벤트는 1년에 한 번만 발생합니다.
You may or may not be rich, it depends on tomorrow!
내일에 따라 당신은 부자가 될 수도 있고 아닐 수도 있습니다!
In that case, I will go with you.
그렇다면 제가 동행해서 가겠습니다.
You can use me as your assistant.
당신은 나를 당신의 조수로 데려갑니다.
You make it sound like it's true.
당신은 그것이 사실인 것처럼 말하고 있습니다.
can you wake up?
일어날 수 있나요?
If you can't wake me up.
깨워줄 수 없으면 깨워주세요.
You woke me up.
당신은 나를 깨웠어요.
OK
좋은.
I'm sleeping now too.
나도 지금 자고 있어요.
I will definitely wake up.
나는 확실히 일어날 수 있다.
Remember, wake me up, okay!
기억해, 날 깨워줘, 알았어!
(Before dawn)
(아직은 밝지 않아요,)
(Is he sleepwalking?)
(그 사람 몽유병인가요?)
[Friendship RS]
[우정RS]
How much is the fare to Jalan Raya No.? 69?
Jalan Raya No.까지 요금은 얼마입니까? 69?
It was still dark and the speed had doubled.
아직 어두워서 비율이 두 배로 늘어났습니다.
Very expensive. It's daybreak now.
매우 비싸다. 이제 일광입니다.
Is it possible to make the price non-negotiable?
가격 협상이 불가능하도록 할 수 있나요?
(Where is he going so early in the morning?)
(이른 아침, 그는 어디로 가고 있나요?)
Okay, that's it.
그럼 그게 다야.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
this morning,
오늘 아침,
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
It seems I don't need to tell you where I'm going.
내가 어디로 가는지 말할 필요는 없을 것 같습니다 .
Where else are you going?
또 어디로 가시나요?
I...
나...
I want to run in the morning.
아침에 달리고 싶다.
The doctor was already walking towards the square.
의사는 이미 광장을 향해 걸어가고 있었다.
There is a bus stop in front.
앞에는 버스 정류장이 있습니다.
Do you run along this route every morning?
매일 아침 이 길을 따라 달리시나요?
Actually, where are you going so early?
사실, 그렇게 이른 아침에 어디로 가시나요 ?
Go to the morning market.
아침시장에 가보세요.
What morning market?
무슨 아침시장?
Today is the annual coffee bean competition.
오늘은 연례 커피콩 대회입니다.
A coffee bean champion is needed to gain representation in China.
중국 대표권을 위해서는 커피빈 챔피언이 필요합니다 .
Fear of failure if you are late.
늦으면 실패에 대한 두려움.
You really don't wake up in the morning with nothing to gain.
당신은 정말로 얻을 것이 없이 아침에 일어날 수 없습니다 .
Go home and rest.
집에 가서 쉬세요.
At half past nine, the first surgery.
9시 반, 첫 작전.
Did you know that the first operation is at half past nine?
첫 작전 이 9시 반인 거 아시죠 ?
If you're late, pay will be deducted, yes.
늦으면 월급 삭감하세요.
clam down.
진정하다.
I would never delay the surgery.
수술을 미루지는 않을 거예요.
I...
나...
I watched until you got in the car.
네가 버스에 탈 때까지 지켜봤어.
Go through the alley in front and you will reach the bus stop.
앞 골목을 지나 버스 정류장에 도착합니다.
Go home and rest.
집에 가서 쉬세요.
Then, I ran all the way to the bus stop.
그리고 는 버스 정류장까지 달려갔습니다.
up to you.
당신한테 달렸습니다.
Don't follow me again.
더 이상 나와 함께 오지 마세요.
There seems to be someone else in front.
앞에 사람들이 있는 것 같습니다.
Something seems wrong.
뭔가 잘못된 것 같습니다.
Oh no.
안 돼.
Why does nothing good happen to you every time I meet you?
왜 만날 때마다 좋은 일이 없을까 ?
let's go.
갑시다.
You hurt Paje and cost him a lot.
당신은 파제에게 큰 손실을 입힐 정도로 상처를 입혔습니다.
You can no longer escape today.
오늘은 더 이상 도망칠 수 없습니다.
Paje? WHO?
파제? WHO?
You helped the driver who caused the accident.
사고를 낸 운전자가 당신을 도왔습니다.
Don't be careless.
부주의하지 마십시오.
You confess to them,
당신은 그들에게 고백합니다.
If you are the person submitting your blood test results to the police?
혈액검사 결과를 경찰에 제출한 사람이 당신이라면 ?
Why?
왜?
Why do you think?
왜 그렇게 생각하세요?
Aren't you worried that he has a grudge against you?
그 사람이 당신에게 원한을 품고 있는 게 아닐까 걱정해서 그런 게 아닐까요?
Why am I so unlucky?
나는 왜 이렇게 운이 좋지 않은 걸까?
Why would I let someone like you follow me?
왜 당신 같은 사람이 나를 따르도록 놔두겠습니까 ?
Not only can't I get money,
돈을 받지 못할 뿐만 아니라,
But my down payment also increased.
하지만 계약금도 올랐어요.
Su Wei'an,kau...
수 웨이안, 카우...
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Stop fighting.
다시 치지 마십시오.
Don't you want money?
너희들은 돈을 원하지 않니?
I'll give you money.
돈을 줄게.
hurry up!
서둘러요!
Come on, hurry up and go.
자, 빨리 가세요.
The police are here.
경찰이 왔습니다.
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Su Wei'an!
수웨이안!
Is your hand okay?
네 손은 괜찮지, 그렇지?
My hands are fine.
내 손은 괜찮아요.
Doctor on call.
근무중인 의사.
Who is the attending physician?
주치의는 누구입니까?
quickly!
빠른!
Boss, why him?
보스, 그 사람은 왜요?
Prepare for tomography now,
즉시 단층촬영을 준비하고,
He was hit in the back of the head.
그의 머리 뒤쪽이 맞았습니다.
Rule out intracranial hemorrhage.
두개내 출혈을 배제하십시오.
quickly!
빠른!
OK
좋은.
(I like.)
(좋아요.)
[RS Zhanghe, Kota Jinhai]
[RS 장허(Zhanghe), 코타진하이(Kota Jinhai)]
Pu Du.
박두.
Data from our second phase of research
우리의 두 번째 단계 연구 데이터
Not as ideal as imagined
기대만큼 이상적이지는 않습니다.
But everything is still under control.
하지만 모든 것이 아직 통제된 단계에 있습니다.
I believe,
나는 믿는다,
As long as the next funds are received on time,
다음 자금이 제때에 들어오는 한,
We can still proceed as planned
우린 여전히 원래 계획을 따를 수 있어
Conduct clinical trials.
임상시험을 개발하기 위해
This process is too slow.
프로세스가 너무 느립니다.
Can you speed up this process?
프로세스 속도를 높일 수 있나요?
I hope,
나는 희망,
It entered clinical trials this year.
올해 임상시험 단계에 돌입했다.
Scientific research must be conducted based on facts.
과학적 연구를 수행하려면 사실에 기초해야 합니다.
I've talked about this from the beginning, when you decide
나는 당신이 결정했을 때 처음부터 이것에 대해 이야기했습니다.
Invest in HDQ39.
HDQ39에 투자하세요.
so,
그래서,
Still can't rush.
아직은 서두르지 못해요.
Yeah.
유모.
Yun Cheng is not an outsider.
윤청은 외부인이 아니다.
Fathers must understand the pressure, too.
아버지들도 압력을 이해해야 합니다.
Dad doesn't know,
아빠는 몰라요
In order to raise funds for dad's research, Yuncheng
아버지의 연구비를 마련하기 위해 윤성
How many drinks have you had with investors?
투자자들과 얼마나 많은 와인을 마셨는가 ?
Pu Du.
박두.
My words are still the same.
내 말은 아직도 똑같다.
Carry out scientific research
과학적 연구 수행
It must be based on facts.
사실에 근거해야 합니다.
Seriousness and vigilance are our basic attitudes.
진지하고 경계하는 것이 우리의 기본 태도입니다.
so,
그래서,
What we are studying is medicine
우리가 연구하는 것은 의학이다
And no other items are checked.
그리고 다른 항목은 검사하지 마세요.
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
You are a local member
당신은 지역 회원입니다
People who study Huntington's disease.
헌팅턴병을 연구하는 사람입니다.
I feel like peace has been handed over
차분한 느낌이 들어요
Research questions for you.
당신을 위한 연구 질문.
You don't need to worry about money, either.
자금에 대해서도 걱정할 필요가 없습니다 .
OK
좋은.
Is your hand okay?
네 손은 괜찮지, 그렇지?
My hands are fine.
내 손은 괜찮아요.
You are hurt.
당신은 다쳤어요.
It hurts, doesn't it?
아프지 않나요?
[Radiology]
[영상의학과]
boss.
보스.
Fortunately there was no intracranial hemorrhage
다행히 두개내 출혈은 없었고 ,
Just a mild concussion.
그냥 가벼운 뇌진탕이에요.
Now you can relax, right?
이제 긴장을 풀 수 있겠죠?
Are you hurt too?
당신도 다쳤나요?
The subject of your writing is just bullshit, right?
당신의 글쓰기 주제는 단지 헛소리입니다, 그렇죠?
Where is your engineer mom?
엔지니어 어머니는 어디 계시나요?
Why does it never appear?
왜 전혀 나타나지 않습니까?
Do n't you have a mother?
엄마가 없을 수도 있나요 ?
A child without a mother is like a grassroots.
엄마 없는 아이들은 풀뿌리와 같습니다.
Your mother doesn't want you anymore.
당신의 어머니는 더 이상 당신을 원하지 않습니다.
You are grassroots.
당신은 풀뿌리입니다.
You can't talk about my mother like that!
우리 엄마에 대해 그런 식으로 말할 수는 없어요!
My mother is in Lakaya.
나의 어머니는 라카야에 계십니다.
He will be back soon.
그는 곧 돌아올 것이다.
How dare you push him. Hit him!
감히 그를 밀어내다니. 그를 때려라!
Your mother doesn't want you anymore.
당신의 어머니는 더 이상 당신을 원하지 않습니다.
You are grassroots.
당신은 풀뿌리입니다.
You are a child without a mother.
당신은 엄마가 없는 아이입니다.
Did you quarrel with other children again?
또 다른 아이들과 말다툼을 하시나요?
They say I don't have a mother.
나한테는 엄마가 없다고 하더라고요.
Remember, don't let me see you lose next time.
다음번에는 당신이 지는 모습을 보여주지 마세요.
Dad, I'm sick.
아빠, 나 아파요.
Tears are the most useless thing
눈물이 제일 쓸데없는 짓이야
In this world.
이 세상에서.
(Why?)
(왜?)
(Why is he willing to die to protect me?)
(왜 그 사람은 나를 보호하기 위해 기꺼이 죽으려고 하는 걸까요 ?)
[Jiang Muying: Bibi Meilan, Wei'an terluka]
[Jiang Muying: Bibi Meilan, Wei'an terluka]
Jiang.
장.
Scallion pancake.
봄 양파 팬케이크.
Just ready to cook.
요리만 하면 됩니다.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Don’t like scallion pancakes?
파 팬케이크를 좋아하지 않습니까?
Wei An was still injured.
웨이안은 여전히 ​​부상을 입었습니다.
Now I should feel guilty
이제 죄책감을 느껴야 하는데,
It is true that I have no appetite for three days.
3일 동안 식욕이 없다면 그건 사실이에요.
However, I saw your scallion pancakes.
그런데 당신의 파전을 봤어요 .
I still want to eat it, it tastes so good.
그래도 먹고 싶은데 냄새가 너무 좋아요.
Why can I be so greedy?
왜 이렇게 욕심이 날 수 있지?
Just eat it.
그냥 먹어요.
no problem.
괜찮아요.
Su Wei'an was already conscious.
Su Wei'an은 이미 의식이 있었습니다.
After all, the Boss has been keeping vigil beside him all night.
결국 보스는 옆에서 경계를 늦추지 않았다.
However,
하지만,
If it weren't for that time, I would have said a lot of things
그땐 내가 말을 많이 하지 않았다면
He couldn't be hurt.
그는 상처받을 리가 없었다.
As you said.
당신이 말하는 것에 따르면.
In case the Boss’s medical skills are not high
사장님이 의료기술이 좋지 않은 경우
and save the driver who caused the accident.
그리고 사고를 낸 운전자를 구해주세요.
If RS de l'Amitie is not a coincidence
RS de l'Amitie 가 우연이 아니라면
Built near the accident site.
사고 현장 근처에 건설됐다.
if not me
내가 아니었다면
Help the driver who caused the accident
사고를 낸 운전자를 도와주세요
Blood alcohol content test.
혈중 알코올 농도 테스트.
If you sell wine,
술을 팔면
Don't sell alcohol to drivers.
운전기사에게 술을 팔지 마세요.
Judging from your words,
당신의 말에서,
Then Su Wei'an couldn't be injured.
그렇다면 Su Wei'an은 부상을 입을 수 없었습니다.
Why do not you say it,
왜 말하지 않았나요?
If Godzilla hadn't saved the world
고질라가 세상을 구하지 않았다면 ,
Then Su Wei'an won't be injured?
그러면 소웨이안은 다치지 않을까요?
It also makes sense.
그것도 말이 되네요.
Can be added next time.
다음에 추가하면 됩니다.
Thanks.
감사합니다.
You still come to comfort me.
아직도 나를 위로하러 오시네요.
(Oh yes!)
(바로 이거 야!)
(current moment)
(현재 순간)
(Coincidence is the best opportunity)
(우연이 최고의 기회다)
(Wei An and Dr. Gu develop a relationship.)
(웨이안과 구 박사는 감정을 키운다.)
(Slightly different from the script)
(대본이랑 좀 다름)
(The hero saves the beauty,)
(영웅은 아름다운 여인을 구한다)
(But the results look much better.)
(하지만 결과는 훨씬 좋아 보입니다.)
(Jiang Muying, your words are unlucky.)
(Jiang Muying, 당신의 말은 운이 좋지 않습니다.)
(You are Cupid in love.)
(당신은 사랑에 빠진 큐피드입니다.)
Gu Yunzheng.
구윤정.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Where is Jiang?
장 어디?
Did you just call me by my name?
방금 내 이름을 불렀나요?
Did you dream about me?
당신은 내 꿈을 꾸나요?
No.
아니요.
If so, why did you call me by my name?
그렇다면 왜 내 이름을 부르는 걸까요?
I...
나...
I want to say that I still owe you money now.
내가 당신에게 빚진 돈은 지금도 있다고 말하고 싶습니다 .
What?
무엇?
Didn't you help me pay the fine at the police station?
경찰서에서 벌금 내는 걸 도와주지 않았나요 ?
This time, my representation failed;
이번에는 나의 대리권이 실패했고,
The down payment and balance were gone, and even I was hurt.
계약금과 최종 잔액이 사라졌고, 나 역시 부상을 입었습니다.
Enough to pay off all my debts.
빚을 모두 갚기에 충분해요.
if not you
당신이 아니라면
Who definitely wants to collect coffee beans and what are they?
커피콩을 꼭 모으고 싶은 사람 , 그게 뭐죠?
Impossible to be chased by bad guys.
나쁜 사람들에게 쫓기는 것은 불가능합니다 .
That...
저것...
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Even if all the bad guys come to attack you.
나쁜 사람들이 다 당신을 공격하러 왔는데도요.
you
너
Sacrifice his life to protect me.
나를 보호하기 위해 목숨을 바쳤습니다.
Is it because my life is precious?
내 생명이 소중해서일까?
Oh, Bernal.
아, 베나르.
Your life is more valuable than mine.
당신의 삶은 나보다 더 비쌉니다.
If you are still alive, you can save many more people.
살아 있으면 더 많은 사람을 구할 수 있습니다 .
Su Wei'an.
수웨이안.
Don't do this again.
다시는 이런 일을 하지 마세요.
no one's life
누구의 생명도 없어
This is worth more than other people's lives.
다른 사람의 생명보다 더 소중한 것입니다 .
Jiang.
장.
Do you know?
알고 계십니까?
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
Will you continue to stay with Wei An here?
여기서 웨이안과 계속 동행하시나요?
Sorry to bother you, you are very considerate.
귀찮게 해서 미안해요, 당신은 매우 배려심이 깊군요.
What precautions?
무슨 관심?
He is my primary doctor.
그는 내 담당 의사입니다.
Isn't this how it should be?
그래야 하는 것 아닌가요?
Understand the patient's condition?
환자의 상태를 이해하려면?
Later you
나중에 당신은
Clean up all the weird stuff
이상한 것 다 청소해
in his mind
그의 머리 속에 있는 것
To avoid wound infection.
상처의 감염을 피하기 위해.
This is medical advice.
이것은 의학적 조언입니다.
OK
좋은.
Wei'an.
웨이안.
I really hope it's me who gets hurt.
상처받는 사람이 바로 저였으면 좋겠습니다 .
You must be very sick because you lost a lot of blood.
피를 많이 흘리니까 많이 아플 것 같아요 .
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
You know I'm not afraid of pain.
내가 고통을 두려워하지 않는다는 걸 당신도 알잖아요.
It will never happen again.
다시는 그런 일이 일어날 수 없습니다.
Don't go anywhere, just stay here.
아무데도 가지 말고 여기에 순종적으로 머물러라.
I know.
알아요.
Oh yes.
바로 이거 야.
Don't tell my mom I'm hurt.
내가 상처받았다는 사실을 어머니에게 말하지 마세요 .
He will be anxious.
그는 매우 불안할 것입니다.
I know.
알아요.
The medical advice given by Dr. Gu is very good.
구 박사님의 의학적 조언은 매우 훌륭했습니다.
Haven't liked it for a long time
오랫동안 마음에 들지 않았어
Look at that weird ponytail of yours.
당신의 이 이상한 포니테일을 보세요.
Give me back the beautiful, smart woman from my medical department.
내 의학부 출신의 아름답고 지적인 여성을 돌려보내세요 .
Jiang Muying.
장무잉.
Who do you support?
당신은 누구를 지지합니까?
Dr. Gu
구박사
Keep waiting for you to wake up.
당신이 깨어날 때까지 계속 기다리십시오.
He really cares about you.
그는 정말로 당신에게 관심을 갖고 있습니다.
Doctors pay attention to patients,
의사는 환자에게 주의를 기울이고,
Isn't this a natural thing?
그건 자연스러운 일이 아닌가?
And you?
당신은 어떤가요?
Blocked the villain's blow for Dr. Gu
구박사를 위한 악당의 일격을 막아냈습니다.
Is this normal?
그것도 정상인가요?
What did I do to save him from getting hit?
그 사람이 맞을 것을 막기 위해 나는 무엇을 했는가 ?
That was not what I meant.
진심이 아니다.
This is his name,
그게 그 사람 이름이에요.
It's too late for me to escape.
늦어서 도망쳤어요.
I'm telling you, yes.
내가 말해줄게, 응.
This time I suffered heavy losses.
이번에는 크게 졌습니다.
I feel that Gu Yunzheng and I are not suitable for each other.
저는 구윤정이랑 안 맞는 것 같아요.
Every time I meet him,
그 사람을 만날 때마다,
The lightest thing is loss,
가장 가벼운 것은 상실이고,
The worst thing that can happen is getting injured.
가장 나쁜 것은 상처받는 것이다.
is this real?
사실인가요?
But maybe Dr. Gu doesn’t think so?
하지만 아마도 구 박사님은 그렇게 생각하지 않으시겠죠?
save life,
생명을 구하다,
Shouldn't we repay it with wedding vows?
결혼 서약으로 보답해야 하는 것 아닌가요 ?
What are your wedding vows?
당신의 결혼 서약은 무엇입니까?
no.
아니다.
It's me who's hurt now
이제 상처받은 건 나야.
Why are you so stupid?
당신의 두뇌는 왜 그렇게 멍청합니까?
Still reciting the wedding vows.
아직도 결혼 서약을 하고 있습니다.
I'm so angry that my head hurts!
너무 짜증나서 머리가 아프다!
Okay, I won't say anymore.
알았어, 더 이상 말 안 할게.
It hurts, doesn't it?
아프지 않나요?
Wei'an.
웨이안.
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
A person has a chance to meet true love in his life,
일생일대의 진정한 사랑을 만날 수 있는 기회 ,
Only three to a billion.
고작 30억~10억.
Therefore, since you have met, you must cherish it.
그러니까 만나셨다면 좋게 평가해야 할 텐데,
do not give up.
포기하지 마십시오.
Only three to a billion?
고작 30억에서 10억 정도?
that opportunity
그 기회
Much less severe than acute illness.
급성 질환보다 훨씬 작습니다 .
When it comes to love and death, it's natural,
사랑과 죽음은 자연스러운 일이지만,
remains a theme in human life.
계속해서 인류의 삶의 주제가 되고 있습니다 .
What are you, dead and seriously ill?
당신은 죽었고 중병을 앓고 있습니까 ?
Just talk every day!
매일 말만 하세요!
It's enough.
이미 충분합니다.
I shouldn't talk nonsense.
함부로 이야기하면 안 된다.
You're talking nonsense again, let's break up!
또 함부로 말하다 우리 헤어지자!
[Friendship RS]
[우정RS]
Gu Yunzheng.
구윤정.
I've tried various types of word combinations,
다양한 단어 조합을 시도해 보았는데 ,
But the complete meaning cannot be assembled.
그러나 완전한 의미를 결합할 수는 없습니다.
It's all over.
끝났습니다.
There is dust.
먼지가 있어요.
you
너
Are you sacrificing your life to protect me because my life is precious?
나를 지키기 위해 목숨을 바친 것은 내 목숨이 소중하기 때문일까?
Your life is more valuable than mine.
당신의 삶은 나보다 더 비쌉니다.
If you are still alive, you can save many more people.
살아 있으면 더 많은 사람을 구할 수 있습니다 .
Damn, this crazy woman.
젠장, 이 미친 여자야.
What on earth was he thinking?
그는 실제로 무엇을 생각하고 있었습니까?
go to hell?
그냥 죽어?
The heroine sacrificed a lot for him,
여주인공은 그를 위해 많은 것을 희생했고,
In the end, he died for him.
결국 여전히 그를 위해 죽습니다.
how come?
왜요?
Until his death, he did not confess his love to the male protagonist.
그는 죽을 때까지 남자주인공에게 사랑을 고백 하지 않았다 .
according to.
베이스.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
We're not slacking off.
우리는 빈둥거리고 있지 않습니다.
It's time to go home from get off work.
이제 퇴근해서 집에 갈 시간이에요.
Please don't tell the head nurse, Doctor Gu.
구 박사님은 간호사에게 말하지 마세요.
I asked you.
나는 당신에게 물었다.
that woman,
그 여자,
Why is he willing to die for the hero?
그는 왜 남주인공을 위해 기꺼이 죽으려고 하는 걸까요 ?
because of love.
사랑 때문에.
She really likes the hero.
그녀는 남자 주연을 정말 좋아합니다 .
I couldn't bear to see him get hurt in the slightest.
그가 조금이라도 상처받는 것을 참을 수 없습니다 .
She chose to sacrifice herself to protect the male protagonist.
그녀는 자신을 희생 하고 남자 주인공을 보호하기로 결정했습니다.
The heroine has done a lot of things for the hero.
여주인공은 남자를 위해 많은 일을 해왔습니다.
But why didn't he admit it?
그런데 그 사람은 왜 인정하지 않는 걸까요?
Gu Yunzheng.
구윤정.
Did you just call me by my name?
방금 내 이름을 불렀나요?
No.
아니요.
That's because women are
그 이유는 여자들이
There is another creature in the mouth and another creature in the heart.
또 다른 생물은 입에 있고 또 다른 생물은 심장에 있습니다.
I want to say that I still owe you money now.
내가 당신에게 빚진 돈은 지금도 있다고 말하고 싶습니다 .
No matter how deep her love for a man is,
남자를 향한 그녀의 사랑이 아무리 깊어도
Will not admit it proactively .
그것을 인정하기 위해 솔선하지 않을 것입니다 .
Whoever admits it first loses.
먼저 인정하는 사람이지 는 사람입니다.
is this real?
사실인가요?
certainly. All drama scripts are written like this.
물론. 드라마 대본은 다 그렇게 쓰여요.
Doctor Gu.
구 박사님.
I'm more professional than you on this matter.
나는 이 문제에 있어서 당신보다 훨씬 더 전문가입니다 .
So that’s it, yes.
알고보니 그렇군요, 네.
Doctor Gu, let’s go first.
구 박사님, 우리 먼저 가겠습니다.
afraid of losing?
지는 것이 두렵나요?
good smell.
매우 향기로운.
Dr. Gu, what a coincidence.
구 박사님, 정말 우연이군요.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I...
나...
I just finished my work.
방금 일을 마쳤어요.
Have you been here long?
여기에 오래 있었나요?
I don't want to disturb your interest
당신의 관심을 방해하고 싶지 않아요
Go to enjoy the flowers in the evening.
밤에 꽃을 즐기기 위해.
very beautiful.
매우 아름답습니다.
Do you like jacaranda flowers too?
자카란다 꽃도 좋아하시나요?
I mean,
내 말은,
You are beautiful like this.
당신은 이렇게 매우 아름답습니다.
That...
저것...
It's getting late.
늦었다.
Go back and rest quickly.
빨리 돌아가서 쉬세요.
(I mean,)
(내 말은,)
(You look so beautiful like this.)
(당신은 이렇게 아름답습니다.)
(Su Weian, what stupid disease do you have?)
(소웨이안 씨, 무슨 병이 있나요?)
(Whether Jiang Muying is infected)
(장무잉이 감염됐나?)
(Or experiencing the side effects of a concussion?)
(또는 뇌진탕으로 인한 부작용이 있습니까 ?)
Did you see Sue at the Hospital de l'Amitie at that time?
그 당시 de l'Amitie 병원에서 Su를 보셨나요 ?
Yes, he hid in the hospital by working as a translator.
그렇죠, 그는 통역사로 병원에 숨었습니다.
Friendship Hospital has a special status.
Hospital de l'Amitie는 특별한 지위를 가지고 있습니다.
We dare not act rashly.
우리는 감히 경솔하게 행동하지 않습니다.
My head is going to explode
머리가 터질 것 같아,
Still need to deal with this issue.
아직 이 일을 처리해야 해요.
Fake wine gives me a headache.
가짜 와인 때문에 머리가 아팠어요.
Call in the Guard.
경비팀을 불러 모으세요.
OK
좋은.
However, General
그러나 장군님,
Dr. Elliot has said,
엘리엇 박사는 이미 이렇게 말했습니다.
All inspection reports
모든 검사 보고서
It means there is nothing wrong with your brain.
당신의 두뇌가 괜찮다는 것을 보여줍니다 .
There were no tumors or bleeding.
종양이나 출혈은 없습니다.
Medical equipment and resources at the French National Hospital
프랑스 국립병원의 의료 장비 및 자원
Always the best in Lakaya.
라카야에서는 항상 최고입니다.
It shouldn't be wrong.
틀려서는 안 됩니다.
Well, hope is the Chinese doctor at Amity Hospital
그럼, 바랍니다. Hospital de l'Amitie의 중국인 의사입니다.
Not so incompetent.
그렇게 무능하진 않을 거에요.
Good morning, Dr. Gu.
좋은 아침입니다, 구 박사님.
Good morning.
좋은 아침이에요.
I heard you were almost injured
다칠 뻔 했다고 들었는데,
Then translation will save you.
그러면 번역가가 당신을 구해줍니다.
You must know how to repay kindness.
은혜를 갚을 줄 알아야 합니다.
Now you buy more supplements and take good care of him.
이제 더 많은 보충제를 구입 하고 그를 잘 돌보십시오.
When your term ends and you return,
임기를 마치고 귀국한 후,
Grandpa must be very grateful to him .
할아버지는 그에게 감사를 표했을 것입니다 .
Okay, grandpa.
알았어, 할아버지.
I will try my best to bring him home.
나는 그를 집에 데려가려고 노력할 것이다 .
Are you still your normal self today ?
오늘도 여전히 평소의 모습인가요 ?
Oh, Bernal.
아, 베나르.
Bibi.
비비.
Please help me make another breakfast today.
오늘 아침 식사를 한 끼 더 만들 수 있도록 도와주세요 .
Great, no problem.
좋아요, 문제 없어요.
And this millet porridge.
이 기장죽도요.
Give me some millet porridge.
기장죽 좀 주세요.
Don't you like to eat millet porridge?
기장죽 먹고 싶지 않니 ?
This millet porridge is made for me.
이 기장죽은 제가 포장할 거예요.
Isn’t this nutritious?
이거 영양가 있지 않나요?
Great, no problem.
좋아요, 문제 없어요.
Add some pickles.
피클을 조금 추가하세요.
OK
좋아요.
Bibi.
비비.
Fill the dumplings with filling and peel them
만두 속을 채우고 껍질을 벗기세요
Aren't you going to sell it?
안 팔아?
Those dumplings don't belong in our cafeteria.
그 만두는 우리 매점에 속하지 않아요.
From skin to content
스킨부터 내용물까지
Not a penny of the organization's money is used.
조직의 돈은 한 푼도 사용하지 않습니다 .
I made some myself to quench my thirst.
갈증을 해소하려고 직접 만들어 봤습니다 .
The content looks very delicious to me.
내용물을 보니 아주 맛있어 보이네요.
That's right, right?
그렇죠?
Look at that small part.
저 작은 부분을 보세요.
Not even enough for me.
나 혼자서도 충분하지 않습니다.
Bibi.
비비.
OK
좋아요.
How do you feel today? do you feel better now?
오늘 기분이 어때요? 기분이 나아졌나요?
A nutritious breakfast per person.
각 1인당 영양가 있는 아침 식사의 일부입니다 .
Eat quickly.
빨리 먹어라.
Ayo.
아요.
However, I haven't ordered a meal yet.
그런데 아직 음식을 주문하지 않았어요.
No purchase required, it's free.
구매할 필요가 없습니다. 무료입니다.
Free? Since when has this been the case?
무료? 언제부터 이랬지?
One copy per patient in neurosurgery.
신경외과 진료 과목은 환자 1인당 1회입니다 .
Are you a patient?
당신은 환자입니까?
Is breakfast free for patients?
환자에게 아침식사는 무료인가요?
This was the special service the doctor recommended for patient number two.
의사가 추천한 2번 환자를 위한 특별 서비스입니다 .
special service?
특별한 서비스?
Come on, Vian, while it's hot.
어서, 웨이안, 더울 때.
So there are also small dumplings?
작은 만두가 있다는 것이 밝혀졌습니다.
Auntie, I really miss this dish.
이 요리가 정말 그리워요, 아줌마.
I also want to eat dumplings.
저도 작은 만두를 먹고 싶어요.
There is only one bowl.
그릇은 하나뿐입니다.
Doctor Fang.
팡 박사님.
your breakfast
당신의 아침 식사
In the cafeteria.
매점에 있어요.
Wait, my heart hurts.
잠깐만요, 마음이 너무 아파요.
Come and see me now.
빨리 나한테 확인해봐.
I also want to eat dumplings.
저도 작은 만두를 먹고 싶어요.
Eat it while it's hot, as recommended by your doctor.
뜨거울 때 먹으십시오. 이것은 의사의 권고에 따른 것입니다.
It turns out you can eat dumplings in Lakaya.
라카야에서는 만두를 먹을 수 있다고 합니다.
This can't happen.
이런 일은 일어날 수 없습니다.
These little dumplings are
이 작은 만두는
Which doctor did you recommend?
어떤 의사를 추천하셨나요?
Boss,
보스,
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
All I know is that you don't have enough work right now.
나는 이제 당신이 할 일이 충분하지 않다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
Hurry up and go through the procedures for extending the hospitalization time for Patient No. 2.
2번 환자의 입원기간 연장 절차를 조속히 처리해 주십시오 .
Extend the course of treatment?
치료기간 연장?
Why extend?
왜 연장되었나요?
I just had a mild concussion.
가벼운 뇌진탕만 있을 뿐입니다.
You can be discharged from the hospital tomorrow , right?
내일 퇴원 해도 되겠죠?
Continue to monitor
계속 모니터링
Prevent delayed intracranial hemorrhage.
지연된 두개내 출혈을 예방하기 위해.
However, I have recovered.
그러나 나는 회복되었습니다.
I'm a doctor.
나는 의사예요.
This is what the doctor recommends.
이것이 의사의 권고입니다.
[Friendship RS]
[우정RS]
♪The night clock continues to tick♪
♪시계는 밤에도 계속 똑딱거리고 있어요♪
♪The noise slowly replaced the silence♪
♪소동이 천천히 침묵을 대신했습니다♪
♪We are performing a meeting script♪
♪ 회의 대본을 연기하고 있습니다 ♪
♪The night is filled with rainbows♪
♪밤에는 무지개가 흩뿌려진다♪
♪With the wind blowing across the desert♪
♪ 사막에 부는 바람과 함께 ♪
♪All this is our testimony♪
♪그 모든 것이 우리의 증인이었어♪
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪However, let’s chase stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, people will lose the direction of what I love♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 사람들은 내가 좋아하는 방향을 잃어버리니까요♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해주는 와인잔을 들고 ♪
♪Let me hug your scars♪
♪네 상처를 안아줄게♪
♪You shine like a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 밝게 빛나네요♪
♪Sparkle when you are alone♪
♪외로울 때 반짝반짝♪
♪The night clock continues to tick♪
♪시계는 밤에도 계속 똑딱거리고 있어요♪
♪The noise slowly replaced the silence♪
♪소동이 천천히 침묵을 대신했습니다♪
♪We are performing a meeting script♪
♪ 회의 대본을 연기하고 있습니다 ♪
♪The night is filled with rainbows♪
♪밤에는 무지개가 흩뿌려진다♪
♪With the wind blowing across the desert♪
♪ 사막에 부는 바람과 함께 ♪
♪All this is our testimony♪
♪그 모든 것이 우리의 증인이었어♪
♪Who doesn’t feel lost in confusion? ♪
♪혼란 속에서 길을 잃지 않는 사람은 누구일까요 ?♪
♪Find one among billions of possibilities♪
♪ 수억 개의 가능성 중 하나를 찾아서 ♪
♪Trapped in a city called destiny ♪
♪운명이라는 도시에 갇혀 ♪
♪However, let’s chase stars♪
♪하지만 여전히 별을 쫓고 있어요♪
♪Don't worry, people will lose the direction of what I love♪
♪걱정하지 마세요. 사람들은 내가 좋아하는 방향을 잃어버리니까요♪
♪Hold a glass of wine to warm your lonely soul♪
♪ 외로운 영혼을 따뜻하게 해주는 와인잔을 들고 ♪
♪Let me hug your scars♪
♪네 상처를 안아줄게♪
♪You shine like a star♪
♪당신은 별처럼 밝게 빛나네요♪
♪Sparkle when you are alone♪
♪외로울 때 반짝반짝♪